Hi guys.
Here I assemble the generator and resonance at the moment.
And so, what I wanted to show you.
The main thing.
The heatsink is barely warm.
Consumption current 1.5 amps.
A 100 watt 12 volt car bulb burns at full brightness.
Here on to this coil and the current clamp.
Look at the current that right now also loaded a small extra load somewhere around 13 ohms.
31.5 amps.
And at the output 12, well, somewhere around 11.8 volts there.
While there, draw your conclusions.
There you go, there's your resonance.
I mean the generator works.
Frequency 14 kilohertz.
Consumption there you go, 24 volts, 1.5 amps.
Here you see, the ammeter is shunted, all as it should be, I mean adjusted.
There you go, the circuit works.
The coil, resonance, and there you go.
The current you see right now at the moment in the coil.
How do you like it?
I think you like it.
Good luck in resonance.